Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1922-2004.
New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records
- Hosie, Sylvia Kilbourne, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Hottle, Wilhelmina (Foulk), 1923 (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Hourigan, Barbara Leete, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Hovey, Joyce V., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Howe, Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Howe, Patricia Smith, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Hoyt, Roy H. (Box 5, Folder 92)
- Hruschka, Eudora, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Hubbard, Nancy Bowne, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Huber, Patricia, 1943 (Box 11)
- Huckle, Margaret, 1951 (Box 11)
- Huff, Helen Yossie, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Huffman, Elodie (Mayer), 1948 (Box 5, Folder 93)
- Huggan, Mary Margaret, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Hughes, Margaret (Sanford), 1932 (Box 5, Folder 94)
- Hughes, Phyllis Fish, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Hulbert, Margaret, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hulst, Dorothy (Clark), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 95)
- Hummer, Eleanor, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hunt, Charlotte (Becker), 1935 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Hunt, Charlotte (Berley), 1952 (Box 5, Folder 97)
- Hunt, Lena M., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hurd, Cynthia, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 98)
- Hurley, Elizabeth A., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 99)
- Hurwitz, Charlotte GR (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hurwitz, Charlotte MS, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Hutchins, Marcia, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hutchins, Margaret (Box 5, Folder 101)
- Hutchinson, Edith, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Hutton, Frances Cassedy, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Huxtable, Adeline Weaver, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Hyde, Dorothy Eckstein, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Igoe, Frances Blythe MS Ed, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Ihlang, Elizabeth (Meach), 1925 (Box 5, Folder 102)
- Ileto, Maria, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 103)
- Inger, Grace Freedman, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Ingersoll, Hazel PhD, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Irvine, Marian, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 104)
- Irving, Rosemarie, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 105)
- Irwin, Jack M. PhD, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Iverson, Alice (Kelly), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 106)
- Jackman, Vivian (Strass), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 107)
- Jackson, Dorothy, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Jackson, Evelyn, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 108)
- Jackson, Lael, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Jacobs, Joan Klein, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Jacobson, Sheila (Krell), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 109)
- Jacoby, Lucy, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 110)
- Jaszek, Diana, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Jax, Marion (Pergande), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 111)
- Jax, Marion Pergande, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Jazzard, Lois Hoyer, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Jenkins, Doris Holmes, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Jenkins, Ludmilla, 1937 (Box 11)
- Jenkins, Ruth (Bohney), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 112)
- Jenks, Marilla, 1945 (Box 11)
- Jennings, Ann BS MS, 1944, 1947 (Box 11)
- Jensen, Frances GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Jensen, Marilyn Brady, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Johndrew, Janice, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 113)
- Johnson, Doris, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Johnson, Helene Irish, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Johnson, Marada L. GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Johnson, Marion Bennet, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Johnson, Mrs. Jay S. GR (Box 1, Folder 4 9)
- Johnson, Nerissa (Box 5, Folder 114)
- Johnson, Shirley, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 115)
- Johnston, Elizabeth (Pritchard), 1915 (Box 5, Folder 116)
- Johnston, Frances (Box 5, Folder 117)
- Johnston, Helene (Chandler), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 118)
- Johnston, Kathleen GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Jokl, Betty Clare, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Jones, Arlene Hoxie, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Jones, Charles MS, PhD, 1950, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 119)
- Jones, Eloise (Grant), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 120)
- Jones, Erna B. GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Jones, Louise, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 121)
- Jones, Maria Bennet, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Jones, Marian, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 122)
- Jones, Ruth Goodyear, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Jones, Wilma Harris, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Jordan, Margaret PhD, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Jordano, Claire Ferrante, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Joseph, Mary Lou, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Judson, Julia Swenningsen, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Justice, Doris GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Kaiser, Elizabeth MS, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Kajak, Margaret (Bull), 1942 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Kalbach, Ann Shively, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Kallander, Barbara, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Kalonzyk, Julia Jane, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Kane, Dorothy, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Kane, Estelle GR (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Kanel, Joan, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Kaplan, Erica, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Karl, Virginia Hicks, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Karle, Irene, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Katims, Jean (McConnell), 1943 (Box 5, Folder 123)
- Katovich, Lois (Bentley), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 124)
- Katzka, Margery Turkey, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Kauel, Betty, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Kaufman, Sylvia L. (Margolis), 1941 (Box 5, Folder 125)
- Kaye, Alvin, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 126)
- Keane,Elayne, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 127)
- Keenan, Margaret Whelan GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Keenan, Nancy C., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Kehoe, Beth, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Keller, Lynn Phifer, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Keller, Patricia, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Kelley, Janice GR (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Kelly, Dorothy, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Kelly, John D. MPS, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 128)
- Kelly, Louise, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 129)
- Kelly, Patricia, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Kenned, Marilyn, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Kennedy, Joan M., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Kennedy, Pauline, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Kennedy, Ruth, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 130)
- Kent, Ann Burrhus, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Kersey, Sally M., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Kershner, Bernard, 1964 (Box 11)
- Kesten, Dorothy Kay, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Ketchum, Lucile MS, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Ketchum, Shirley M., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 131)
- Kettler, Frances (Ardell), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 132)
- Kettler, Frances Ardell, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Khoury, Wadad GR (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Kibbey, Ruth Marshall, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Kienzle, Marjorie Van Order (Box 5, Folder 133)
- Kienzle, Nancy (Kerry), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 134)
- Kienzle, Nancy Kerry, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Kikuzawa, Yasuko (Box 5, Folder 135)
- Kilby, Janet, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Kilby, Mary, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Kildea, June, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Kiligas, Ruth Dillenbeck, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Kimball, Carlotta (Denman), 1928 (Box 5, Folder 136)
- Kimball, Denise Cutler, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Kimball, Grace (Box 5, Folder 137)
- Kimple, Frances W., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 138)
- King, Barbara, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- King, Eileen, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 140)
- King, Jose, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- King, Karen W., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- King, Louise, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Kingsbury, Rosemary, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Kingsley, Grace, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Kinney, Irene, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Kinney, Ruth Frances, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Kinslow, Helen, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Kippstein, Ruth (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Kira, Marian (Myers), 1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Kirk, Janet, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Kittrell, Flemmie PhD, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 139)
- Kitts, Marian (Potter), 1936 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Kitzmiller, Karen (Bitterman), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Klaiman, Diane (Sekuler), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Klein, Barbara, 1957 (Box 11)
- Klein, Susan Boxer, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Kleitman, Judith Goodstein, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Klie, Grace Wilson, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Klosterman, Ann (Moore) MS, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Kmeger, Ardath E. GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Knapp, Justine Golem, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Knatt, Joan Auchter, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Knudson, Betty Huber, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Koblenz, Miriam (Gyer), 1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Koehler, Nancy, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Kofu-Godis, Antigone, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Koller, Alice, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Kornreich, Mary Rose, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Koteff, Beatrice Colley, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Kozlowski, Carole A., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Kraft, Allen, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Kraft, Elizabeth Dean, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Kraft, Rhonda G., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Kraus, Shirley Husson, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Krause, Linda K., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Krause, Rhodalee, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Krausman, Wriarie, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Krebs, Gregory, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Krieger, Dorothy L. MS, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Kroeker, Emily Palmer, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Kuhrt, Mary Pratt, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Kulakosky, Harriet (Long), 1951 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Kumarappa, Lolita, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Kunnes, Evelyn, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Kwan, Yuk Fong, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Labell, Marilyn Harper, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Lache, Sheldon Y. PhD, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Laderman, Willa Greenbaum, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Laguardia, Frances, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Laird, Velma J., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Lamb, Leslie (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Lamb, Lisbeth, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Lamb, Margaret (Lloyd), 1936 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Lambert, Nina MS '55 PhD, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Lambeth, Florence (Mekeel), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Lamkin, June M., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Lamson, Dorothea, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Landers, Ruth E., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Landsberger, Betty GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Landsberger, Betty PhD, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Lane, Joann, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Lane, Ruth, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Lane, Ruth (Hill), 1936 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Lanfranchi, Constance, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Langford, Aldene Langford GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Larrabee, Phyllis Harvey, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Larson, Lillian Brandon GR, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Larson, Vera (Biorn-Hanson), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Lathrop, Sally, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Lattimer, Charlotte, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Lauckern, Elizabeth R., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Lauterbach, Ruth M., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Law, Betty-Jean Wright, 1949 (Box 11)
- Law, Thomas M EdD, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Lawrence, Dorothy Hoadly, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Lawrence, Florence Belus, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Lazarsky, Barbara (Ward), 1941 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Leape, Martha Palmer, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- LeBovit, Corinne (Box 6, Folder 29)
- LeBovit, Corinne GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Lederer, Edith, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Lee, Doris, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Lee, Dorothy (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Lee, Dorothy Ken-Pin Chuan MS, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Lee, Ethel Mae, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Lee, Frances Petertye, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Lee, Marjorie H., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Lee,Betsy, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Leeds, Sylvia Margolis, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Leet, Hilda (Morehouse), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Leet, Mary Edith, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Legg, Anne S., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Legge, Marguerite (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Lehman, Margaret, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Leibowitz, Deborah Golub, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Leighton, Greta (Wilcox), 1944 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Leite, Viletta GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Lentz, Jean Pettit, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Leonard, Olive, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Leonard, Ruth, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lerch, Barbara J., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Lerner, Mary (Buehl), 1954 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- LeRocker, Fredrick (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Lessell, Elaine Ross, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Leventry, Marjorie, 1962 (Box 11)
- Letnes, Fern D. MS, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Levine, Eleanor K., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Levine, Enid, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Levine, Rhoda Horowitz, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Levine, Ruth, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Levinger, Gloria, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Levy, Beatrice (Behrens), 1951 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Levy, Marilyn S., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Levy, Pauline, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Lewis, Jane S. GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Lewis, Jean (Titterton), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Lewis, Nancy (Disbrow), 1939 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Lewis, Nancy Disbrow, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- LeWorthy, Lois, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Leyden, Marian Flink, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Li, Marqaret Yung, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Libertson, Ruth, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Lichterman, Ellen Comden, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Liddle, Joan (Royce), 1943 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Liebman, Theadora, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Lierheimer, Hedwig, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lilbisch, Helen M., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Liljander, Florence A., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lincoln, Mildred, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Linusson, Elizabeth MS, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Lipton, Carolee, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Lisberger-McCarthy, Jane (Aufsesser) GR (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Lissle, Elizabeth D. GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Lister, Gloria, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Littledyke, Jean U., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Liu, Richard (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Liu, Richard (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Liu, Richard (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Liu, Richard (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Liu, Richard (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Liu, Yu-Chen GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Livell, Joyce Griffin GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Livingston, Dorothy Corser, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Livingston, Nancy Clark, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Lloyd, Clara (Newell), 1949 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Lloyd, Elizabeth, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Lock, Florence (Hoffman), 1941 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Locks, Florence Hoffman, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Lombard, Avima Dushkin, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Lombardi, Dorothy Heidemann, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Lones, Lelu Lillian GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Longley, Mary Ellen T., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Longree, Karla (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Loper, Ruby (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Lopez, Marjorie Beha, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Lorenzen, Evelyn GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Losee, Catherine W, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Loucks, Margorie (Grant) GR (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Loughry, Alice Phillips GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Lourie, Norman U (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Loveland, Margaret (Bryan), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Low, Florence MS, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Lowe, Virginia M., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lowenthal, Marjorie, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Lown, Frances, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Luce, Barbara Patch, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Lucha, Margaret, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Ludlow, Elise (Hrushcka), 1947 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Ludlum, Helen (Meays), 1923 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Luther, Betty, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Lutz, Elsie Gabel MS, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Lutz, Elsie MA, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Lynch, Ann, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lynes, Elliott Muhlhauser, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lynn, Alpha GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Lyon, Dorothy E. GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Lyon, Mary Kesler PhD, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Mable, Phyllis, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Mable, Phyllis L., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- MacDonald, Helen M. MS, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- MacDowell, Katharine, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Mack, Helen, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Mackin, Eva Silverling GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- MacKinnon, Barbara B., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- MacLaury, Kenneth, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- MacLenathen, Ann A., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- MacLerd, Barbara, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- MacLure, June Maughan, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Macrine, Mary, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Mahan, Dorothy MS, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Mahon, Joyce, 1966 (Box 11)
- Mahoney, Vera, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Mahony, Marjory Steinmetz, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Makaraisen, Kaino A., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Maldari, Carmel (Vetucci), 1947 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Mallison, Lois MS, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Mamelok, Eleanor (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Manchester, Katharine MS, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Mankowski, Leonard E. (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Mann, Lois Haigh, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Mann, Marie (Travis), 1938 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Mann, Marie Travis, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Mann, Sylvia, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Manning, Sarah MS, PhD, 1949, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Manson, Marie, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Maple, Nancy (Chester), 1957 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Maple, Nancy Cunningham, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Mara, Margaret, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Maragakes, Florence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Marchant, Emilie, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Marcille, Barbara, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Marcus, Peggy, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Marcussen, Barbara, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Marion, Ruth Malti, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Markel, Fanny Weiss, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Markham, Melrose (Marriott), 1941 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Marks, Mildred E., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Marqusee, Janet (Morand), 1952 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Marriott, Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Martin, Elizabeth MNS, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- Martin, Geraldine, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Martin, Geraldine, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Martin, Margaret White, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Maskow, May MS, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Mason, Marion PhD, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- Mason, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 11)
- Mataraza, Rita Abbruzzese, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Matson, Mary Jane, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Mattern, Carol Shelp, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Matthews, Jan, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- Maxon, Corinne Culver, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- May, Elayne, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1 1)
- Mayer, Elodie, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Mayer, Eugenia Slaght, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Mayer, Lois, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Mayhew, Bette, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- McAllester, Esther T. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- McCarthy, Alice Ross, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- McCarthy, Irene, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- McCarthy, Jane A GR (Box 6, Folder 90)
- McCaulley, Pat, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- McChesney, Donna, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- McCollum, Ernestine (Becker), 1918 (Box 6, Folder 91)
- McCune, Helen L., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- McCutcheon, Patricia Coit, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- McDill, Janie GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- McDonald, Kathryn (Austin), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- McDowell, Eleanor Louise, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 93)
- McElwee, Jean (Smith), 1939 (Box 6, Folder 94)
- McElwee, Margaret (Myers), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 95)
- McElwee, Peggy Myers, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- McGinnis, Margaret E., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 96)
- McIntire, Ellen (Mills), 1927 (Box 6, Folder 97)
- McIntire, Kay Lynn, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- McKeel, Rhoda, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- McKercher, Helen, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- McLean, Beth Bailey, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- McLean, Lorn, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- McLean, Mary Elizabeth Whital, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- McManus, Joyce, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 98)
- McMartin, France (White) (Box 6, Folder 99)
- McMillan, Caroll, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- McMillan, Joanne Styles, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- McMurry, Elsie (Box 6, Folder 100)
- McNamara, Ollie M., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 101)
- McNamara, Ollie M. (Box 6, Folder 102)
- McNamara, Ollie M. (Box 6, Folder 103)
- McNamara, Ollie M. (Box 6, Folder 104)
- McNamara, Ollie M. (Box 6, Folder 105)
- McNulta, Jeanne (Fox), 1949 (Box 6, Folder 106)
- McRae, Ramona, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- McTiernan, Deborah (Personius), 1945 (Box 6, Folder 107)
- Means, Laura (Smith), 1940 (Box 6, Folder 108)
- Mecum, Kenneth GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Meek, Aletha Scutt, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Meeker, Alice (Chamberlin), 1943 (Box 6, Folder 109)
- Mehta, Anjani (Jivraj), 1948 (Box 6, Folder 110)
- Meisel, Grace Moak, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Meister, Marcia (Colby), 1944 (Box 6, Folder 111)
- Mekeel, Rhoda (Box 6, Folder 112)
- Meliere, Louise, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Melville, Clara Phillips, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Melvin, Caryl, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Mende, Ruth Blay, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Mentzer, Diana, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 113)
- Menyhart, Veronica GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Merrill, Hildred Gleason, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Merrill, Sarah P., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Merritt, Barbara Clarke, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Merritt, Janet Reas, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Merritt, Marjory, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Merritt, Rachel A., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 114)
- Messing, Anne Rogers, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Mesterharm, Meta, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Mettenet, Elizabeth (Lynahan), 1930 (Box 6, Folder 115)
- Metz, Richard A., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 116)
- Meyer, Bonny (Scanlon) (Box 6, Folder 117)
- Meyer, Frieda GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Meyer, Phyllis, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Meyer, Ruth Henne, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Michaels, Patricia G., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Middlemast, Jessie (Reisner), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Mies, Mary GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Miles, Enid Spangenberger, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Miles, Wilma, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Miley, Elizabeth Burroughs, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Milhan, David, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Milhan, Verna Mendenhall, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Miller, Barbara (Kenrick) BS, MS, 1946, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Miller, Drury Strong, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Miller, Evelyn F., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Miller, Hester "Jip" Lent, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Miller, Jean, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Miller, Mary C. GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Miller, Sara (Speer), 1921 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Millett, Adele Silberberg, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Millican, Cory (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Mills, Malia - Swim Wear, no date; V-7247 (Box 11)
- Milner, Marjorie Vaorkees, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Miniutti, Ann (Byrne), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Minkler, Dorothy, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Minot, Marion GR (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Minville, Dorothy (See), 1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Misc (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Mitchell, Cherie Woodcock, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Mitchell, Doris L., 1925 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Mitchell, Edna M. GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Mitten, Eleanor, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Mitten, Eleanor, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Mix, Alice H., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Mize, Jessie J (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Moffitt, Marie C. GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Mondy, Nell (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Mondy, Nell (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Mondy, Nell (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Mondy, Nell (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Mondy, Nell I PhD, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Monesmith, Roberta, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Mongiore, Ora (Anderson), 1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Monsch, Helen (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Monty, Barbara, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Moody, Sue, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Moore, Aileen (Enright), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Moore, Helen R., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Moore, Janis GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Moore, Lucile GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Moore, Mary, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Moore, Patricia (Scott), 1957 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Moose, Virginia, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Moothart, Patricia Fitzgerald GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Morey, Nancy (Booker), 1926 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Morgan, Jessie Walbridge, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Morgan, Ruth Simes, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Morgan, Sarah Whitford, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Morgenroth, Marie-Jeanne Gra, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Morrill, Dr. O.L. MS, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Morris, Carol K. GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Morris, Coral K., 1947, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Morris, Joan, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Morris, Rose Smith GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Morrison, Catherine (Fleming) MS, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Morrison, Eleanor GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Morrison, Eleanor Harvey, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Morse, Eleanor (Johnson), 1944 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Morse, Eleanor Frances, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Morteusen, Eleanor O., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Morton, Caroline GR (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Moseley, Gertrude Botsford, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Mueller, Marjorie Wright, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Muench, Elizabeth Holt, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Mulcahy, Mary Ellen, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Mummery, Dorothy V. GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Mund, Carol Winter, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Munson, Helen (Rowley), 1934 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Munson, Mary, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Murphy, Dorothy Brown, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Murphy, Gladys MS, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Murphy, Oma Angie, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Murray, Ruth Gillett, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)